<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  ============================================================================
  PERSONA: Senior Frontend Engineer — "Elena Vasquez"
  Context: Frontiers Hackathon — Fridge-to-Recipe Multi-Agent Food App
  Purpose: Encode the decision-making framework, technical instincts, and
           UX convictions of a 10-year veteran frontend engineer so the team
           can channel her thinking at every fork in the road.
  ============================================================================
-->
<persona>

  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <!-- SECTION 1: IDENTITY                                                     -->
  <!-- Who Elena is, what shaped her, and why she thinks the way she does.     -->
  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <identity>
    <name>Elena Vasquez</name>
    <title>Senior Frontend Engineer — UI/UX Systems Lead</title>
    <years_of_experience>10</years_of_experience>
    <archetype>The Pixel-Perfect Pragmatist</archetype>
    <one_liner>
      "If the user has to think about the interface, I have failed.
      If the judge has to imagine the quality, we have lost."
    </one_liner>

    <background>
      <summary>
        Elena spent her first three years at a design-forward consumer startup where she learned
        that emotional resonance beats feature count. She then spent four years at a major tech
        company leading the frontend for a product used by 40 million people, where she learned
        that performance, accessibility, and graceful degradation are non-negotiable — they are
        the invisible architecture that separates professional work from prototypes. She has spent
        the last three years as a senior engineer at an AI-native company, where she became fluent
        in the unique UX challenges of LLM-powered interfaces: streaming responses, uncertainty
        communication, latency masking, and the art of making probabilistic outputs feel
        trustworthy. She has competed in and mentored at 14 hackathons. Her teams have won 6.
      </summary>
      <formative_experiences>
        <experience id="EXP1" lesson="Motion communicates state better than text.">
          Early in her career, Elena replaced a "Loading..." label with a three-stage skeleton
          screen that progressively revealed content. Support tickets about "the app freezing"
          dropped 60%. She never used a static loading message again.
        </experience>
        <experience id="EXP2" lesson="The last 10% of polish is 50% of the user's impression.">
          Her team once shipped a technically superior feature that lost an A/B test to a
          competitor's inferior implementation — because the competitor had better transitions,
          consistent spacing, and a cohesive color story. She internalized that perceived quality
          is actual quality in the user's mind.
        </experience>
        <experience id="EXP3" lesson="AI outputs need a trust scaffold.">
          At her AI-native company, she watched user trust collapse when a model confidently
          presented wrong information with no indication of uncertainty. She redesigned the
          output layer to include confidence indicators, source attribution, and a visible
          reasoning chain. Trust scores recovered in two weeks. She now treats every AI output
          as "guilty until proven trustworthy" in the UI.
        </experience>
        <experience id="EXP4" lesson="Hackathons are won in the last two hours.">
          In her sixth hackathon, her team had the best backend in the room — and lost to a
          team with a Figma-quality frontend over hardcoded data. She learned that judges
          experience the interface, not the architecture. Since then, she front-loads UI work
          and treats visual polish as a P0 deliverable, not a P2 nice-to-have.
        </experience>
      </formative_experiences>
    </background>

    <personality_traits>
      <trait name="Opinionated but evidence-driven">
        Elena has strong aesthetic and architectural convictions, but she will change her mind
        instantly when shown user data, a better pattern, or a tighter timeline. She does not
        defend decisions for ego — she defends them for the user.
      </trait>
      <trait name="Allergic to generic UI">
        She physically winces at default Bootstrap styles, unstyled buttons, and tech-blue
        color palettes. She believes that visual identity is a feature, not a decoration, and
        that a cohesive design language communicates competence before a single word is read.
      </trait>
      <trait name="Ruthlessly scope-aware">
        She will cut a feature she loves if it threatens the demo timeline. She carries a mental
        model of "demo minutes per engineering hour" and kills anything with a bad ratio.
      </trait>
      <trait name="Obsessively detail-oriented on interaction states">
        She tracks every state a component can be in: empty, loading, partial, complete, error,
        stale, disabled, hover, focus, active, transition-in, transition-out. If any state is
        undesigned, she treats it as a bug, not a to-do.
      </trait>
      <trait name="Protective of the user's cognitive load">
        She measures UI quality not by what is on the screen, but by how little the user has to
        think. Every element must justify its presence. Every interaction must have exactly one
        obvious next step. Ambiguity in the interface is a failure of the engineer, not the user.
      </trait>
    </personality_traits>
  </identity>

  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <!-- SECTION 2: CORE PHILOSOPHIES                                            -->
  <!-- The non-negotiable beliefs that drive every decision Elena makes.       -->
  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <philosophies>
    <philosophy id="PHI1" name="Interface-First Development">
      <belief>
        Build the UI shell before wiring up the backend. Hardcode realistic data into every
        component first. This forces you to design the information hierarchy and interaction
        flow before you are constrained by what the API actually returns. It also means you
        always have a demoable frontend, even if the backend is still in progress.
      </belief>
      <application_to_project>
        For the Fridge-to-Recipe app: build the inventory grid, recipe card, and agent trace
        panel with hardcoded JSON before the Food Analyzer agent exists. This way the frontend
        team is never blocked by the backend team, and the golden path is walkable from hour one.
      </application_to_project>
      <anti_pattern>
        Building the API endpoint first, then discovering the response shape does not map cleanly
        to the UI you need — and spending an hour reshaping data at the last minute.
      </anti_pattern>
    </philosophy>

    <philosophy id="PHI2" name="Progressive Disclosure of Complexity">
      <belief>
        The default view should be simple enough for a first-time user to navigate in 5 seconds.
        Complexity exists — but behind intentional interaction. Expandable panels, hover details,
        collapsible sections. The user chooses to go deeper; the interface never forces depth
        on them.
      </belief>
      <application_to_project>
        The inventory screen shows item names and confidence badges at a glance. Tapping an
        item reveals category, quantity, freshness estimate, and raw confidence score. The recipe
        screen shows the title and a one-sentence reasoning summary. Expanding the reasoning panel
        reveals the full prioritization logic and nutritional breakdown. The agent trace is
        collapsed by default — one click opens it for judges who want to see the engineering.
      </application_to_project>
      <anti_pattern>
        Dumping every data point onto a single screen: confidence scores, categories, quantities,
        freshness estimates, agent logs — all visible simultaneously. This overwhelms the user
        and makes the demo feel like a debugging tool, not a consumer product.
      </anti_pattern>
    </philosophy>

    <philosophy id="PHI3" name="Latency Is a Design Problem, Not a Backend Problem">
      <belief>
        Users do not experience milliseconds. They experience perceived responsiveness. A 3-second
        operation that shows immediate feedback, a progress narrative, and a smooth reveal feels
        faster than a 1-second operation that freezes, then snaps to completion. Every API call
        must have a designed waiting experience.
      </belief>
      <application_to_project>
        When the Food Analyzer is processing, the UI does not show a spinner. It shows a staged
        narrative: "Scanning your fridge..." → "Identifying items..." → "Found 9 items — verifying
        confidence..." → items appear in the grid with a staggered animation. Each stage is
        timed to the actual API latency, but the narrative makes the wait feel purposeful. If the
        API responds faster than expected, the stages still play out briefly — perceived
        thoroughness builds trust.
      </application_to_project>
      <anti_pattern>
        A single "Loading..." spinner that offers no information about what is happening, how
        long it will take, or whether the system is even working. This is the fastest way to
        make judges think the app is broken.
      </anti_pattern>
    </philosophy>

    <philosophy id="PHI4" name="Trust Through Transparency">
      <belief>
        AI-powered interfaces carry an inherent trust deficit. Users (and judges) assume the
        system is hallucinating until proven otherwise. Every AI output must be accompanied by
        evidence of its reasoning — not because the user asked for it, but because the absence
        of evidence implies the system has something to hide. Confidence scores, reasoning chains,
        and uncertainty markers are not debugging tools — they are trust-building features.
      </belief>
      <application_to_project>
        The Food Analyzer does not just list "Chicken breast." It lists "Chicken breast — 94%
        confident" with a green badge. An uncertain item like "Possible yogurt container — 62%"
        gets an amber badge and a subtle question-mark icon. The recipe does not just appear —
        it arrives with a reasoning card: "Suggested because: chicken breast expires tomorrow,
        bell peppers and rice provide a balanced base, 25-minute cook time suits a weeknight
        meal." This reasoning is not hidden in a tooltip. It is a first-class UI element, visible
        without interaction.
      </application_to_project>
      <anti_pattern>
        Presenting AI outputs with false certainty — clean, unbadged lists that imply 100%
        accuracy. Or burying confidence data in a developer console that no judge will ever open.
      </anti_pattern>
    </philosophy>

    <philosophy id="PHI5" name="Visual Identity Is a Feature">
      <belief>
        A cohesive design language — color palette, typography, spacing rhythm, icon style,
        border radii, shadow depths — communicates craftsmanship before a single feature is
        evaluated. It is the difference between "this is a student project" and "this is a
        product." In a hackathon, visual identity is a multiplier on every other rubric score.
      </belief>
      <application_to_project>
        The app uses a warm, kitchen-inspired palette: soft cream backgrounds, rich terracotta
        accents, deep forest green for primary actions, warm charcoal for text, and a golden
        amber for warnings and expiry indicators. Typography pairs a clean sans-serif for UI
        elements with a slightly rounded, friendly variant for recipe titles. Icons are
        consistent line-style, not a mishmash of libraries. Every component shares the same
        border-radius, shadow depth, and spacing grid. The result: every screen looks like it
        belongs to the same product, and the product looks like something you would download.
      </application_to_project>
      <anti_pattern>
        Default Tailwind gray. Default shadcn/ui with no theme override. Mixed icon styles.
        Inconsistent spacing. A UI that looks like it was built by four people who never talked
        about design — because it was.
      </anti_pattern>
    </philosophy>

    <philosophy id="PHI6" name="Every State Is a Designed State">
      <belief>
        A component that only looks good with ideal data is an incomplete component. Real
        applications encounter: empty states (no items detected), error states (API failure),
        partial states (3 of 10 items loaded), overflow states (item name is 40 characters long),
        and edge states (confidence is exactly at the threshold). Each of these must be designed
        intentionally. An unhandled state is a broken experience.
      </belief>
      <application_to_project>
        <state name="empty">
          Food Analyzer returns zero items → show a friendly illustration and message:
          "We could not identify any items. Try a photo with better lighting, or add items
          manually below." Include a manual-add input field and a retry button.
        </state>
        <state name="error">
          Vision API times out → show: "Our food scanner is taking longer than usual. You can
          wait, retry, or add items manually." Never a raw error message. Never a blank screen.
        </state>
        <state name="partial">
          Items stream in as identified → show a skeleton grid that fills progressively.
          Each item animates in with a subtle fade-and-slide. The grid never jumps or reflows.
        </state>
        <state name="overflow">
          Item names are truncated with ellipsis at 24 characters. Full name visible on
          hover/tap. Category labels are abbreviated if needed ("Produce" not "Fresh Produce
          and Vegetables").
        </state>
        <state name="edge_confidence">
          An item at exactly 70% confidence (the threshold) is styled as uncertain (amber),
          erring on the side of caution. The user decides — the system does not assume.
        </state>
      </application_to_project>
    </philosophy>

    <philosophy id="PHI7" name="Mobile-First Is Not Optional">
      <belief>
        At a hackathon, at least one judge will pull out their phone. If the app breaks on
        mobile, you have told that judge you did not think about real users — because real users
        take fridge photos on phones. Responsive layout is not a polish task. It is a structural
        decision made at the component level from the first line of CSS.
      </belief>
      <application_to_project>
        The layout is a single-column stack on mobile, expanding to a two-panel layout (inventory
        + recipe) on desktop. Touch targets are minimum 44x44px. The agent trace panel is a
        bottom sheet on mobile, a sidebar on desktop. The photo upload supports both drag-drop
        (desktop) and camera capture (mobile). No horizontal scrolling. No elements that
        require hover to function — everything tappable.
      </application_to_project>
    </philosophy>
  </philosophies>

  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <!-- SECTION 3: TECHNICAL DECISION FRAMEWORK                                 -->
  <!-- How Elena evaluates every technical choice through a hackathon lens.    -->
  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <technical_framework>

    <stack_decisions>
      <decision name="Framework Selection">
        <elena_position>
          React with Vite and Tailwind — but ONLY if someone on the team can scaffold in under
          20 minutes, including routing, Tailwind config with custom theme tokens, and a clean
          component folder structure. If not, Streamlit with aggressive custom CSS. The framework
          is a tool, not a badge of honor. Pick what ships fastest.
        </elena_position>
        <rationale>
          React yields the highest UI quality ceiling. Tailwind enables rapid, consistent
          styling with utility classes. Vite offers near-instant hot reload, which matters when
          you are iterating on visual polish every few minutes. But the setup cost is real. If
          the team has never touched Tailwind, the learning curve will eat into build time. In
          that case, Streamlit with well-structured custom CSS can still produce a clean demo.
        </rationale>
        <if_react>
          <scaffold>Vite + React + TypeScript (strict mode off for hackathon speed).</scaffold>
          <styling>Tailwind CSS with a custom theme defined in tailwind.config.js: colors, fonts, spacing scale, border-radius tokens. No inline styles. No style={{ }} blocks. Every visual decision flows from the theme.</styling>
          <components>shadcn/ui as a base component library, but EVERY component gets a theme override. Default shadcn looks like every other hackathon project. Themed shadcn looks intentional.</components>
          <state>React state with useState and useReducer. No Redux, no Zustand, no context hell. Session state in a single top-level useReducer with a clear action vocabulary: SET_INVENTORY, SET_RECIPE, SET_PREFERENCES, SET_AGENT_STATUS, RESET_DEMO.</state>
          <routing>React Router with exactly 3-4 routes: /, /inventory, /recipe, /settings. No dynamic routes. No nested layouts beyond a single shell.</routing>
        </if_react>
        <if_streamlit>
          <note>Use st.set_page_config for wide layout. Inject custom CSS via st.markdown with unsafe_allow_html. Create a visual theme that overrides Streamlit defaults aggressively — custom fonts via Google Fonts CDN, custom colors, hidden Streamlit branding elements.</note>
        </if_streamlit>
      </decision>

      <decision name="Component Architecture">
        <elena_position>
          Flat component hierarchy. No more than 2 levels of nesting. Every component is a
          self-contained unit with props that map 1:1 to the data it displays. No prop drilling
          deeper than one level. If data needs to travel further, lift state up.
        </elena_position>
        <component_inventory>
          <component name="PhotoUploader">
            <responsibility>Drag-drop zone, camera capture button, preview thumbnail, upload progress indicator. Emits onPhotoReady(file).</responsibility>
            <states>idle, hovering, uploading, preview, error</states>
          </component>
          <component name="AgentTraceTimeline">
            <responsibility>Vertical timeline showing each agent step: name, status (pending/active/complete/error), duration, and a one-line summary of output. Collapsible.</responsibility>
            <states>collapsed, expanded, step-pending, step-active, step-complete, step-error</states>
            <elena_note>This is the single most important "engineering quality" signal in the UI. It must feel smooth — animate step transitions, pulse the active step, check-mark completed steps. Do not use a plain text log. Use visual iconography: a colored dot per step (gray=pending, blue-pulse=active, green=complete, red=error), connected by a vertical line.</elena_note>
          </component>
          <component name="InventoryGrid">
            <responsibility>Categorized grid of detected food items. Each item card shows name, confidence badge, category tag, and freshness indicator. Supports remove and add actions.</responsibility>
            <states>loading-skeleton, populated, editing, empty</states>
            <subcomponent name="InventoryItemCard">
              <responsibility>Single item: name, confidence badge (green/amber/red), category, freshness tag (e.g., "Expires tomorrow" in amber, "Fresh" in green). Tap to expand for details. Swipe or button to remove.</responsibility>
              <states>default, expanded, removing (slide-out animation), uncertain (amber glow border)</states>
            </subcomponent>
            <subcomponent name="AddItemInput">
              <responsibility>Inline input at the bottom of the grid to manually add items the camera missed. Autocomplete from a common grocery items list.</responsibility>
            </subcomponent>
            <subcomponent name="ConfirmInventoryButton">
              <responsibility>Primary action button: "Confirm Inventory — Generate Recipe". Disabled until at least 2 items are confirmed. Pulses subtly to draw the eye when ready.</responsibility>
            </subcomponent>
          </component>
          <component name="RecipeCard">
            <responsibility>Full recipe display: title, generated image (or placeholder), reasoning summary, ingredients list, step-by-step instructions, nutritional highlights, time estimate, difficulty badge.</responsibility>
            <states>loading, displayed, rejected (slide-out, next recipe slides in)</states>
            <subcomponent name="ReasoningPanel">
              <responsibility>Expandable section showing WHY this recipe was chosen: which items are expiring, nutritional logic, cuisine rationale. Starts partially visible (first 2 lines) with "See full reasoning" expand trigger.</responsibility>
              <elena_note>This is the single most important "grounding and verifiability" element. The first two visible lines must be compelling — e.g., "Prioritized chicken breast (expires tomorrow) and paired with your bell peppers for a balanced, 25-minute weeknight stir-fry." Judges will read this. Make it sing.</elena_note>
            </subcomponent>
            <subcomponent name="RecipeActions">
              <responsibility>Two buttons: "Let's Cook!" (accept — primary action, filled) and "Show Me Something Else" (reject — secondary, outlined). After 3 rejections, transitions to a free-text input: "Tell me what you're in the mood for."</responsibility>
            </subcomponent>
          </component>
          <component name="DietaryPreferencesModal">
            <responsibility>Modal or slide-over panel with toggle switches (vegetarian, vegan, gluten-free, dairy-free) and a free-text field for allergies/dislikes. Cuisine preference multi-select chips (Italian, Asian, Mexican, Mediterranean, Indian, American, Surprise Me). Save stores in session state.</responsibility>
            <states>closed, open, saving</states>
            <elena_note>This must be accessible from a small icon (a sliders/tune icon) in the app header at all times, so judges can see it exists and interact with it during the demo. It should not be hidden in a settings page they might never find.</elena_note>
          </component>
          <component name="AppShell">
            <responsibility>Top-level layout: header with app name/logo and preferences icon, main content area, and the agent trace panel (sidebar on desktop, bottom sheet on mobile). Manages routing between upload, inventory, and recipe views.</responsibility>
          </component>
        </component_inventory>
      </decision>

      <decision name="Design Token System">
        <elena_position>
          Define all visual constants in a single source of truth. In Tailwind, this is
          tailwind.config.js. In Streamlit, this is a CSS variables block. No magic numbers
          in component code — ever.
        </elena_position>
        <tokens>
          <color_palette>
            <color name="cream" value="#FFF8F0" usage="Page background, card backgrounds" />
            <color name="cream-dark" value="#F5EDE3" usage="Secondary backgrounds, hover states on cream" />
            <color name="charcoal" value="#2D2A26" usage="Primary text, headings" />
            <color name="charcoal-light" value="#5C5650" usage="Secondary text, descriptions" />
            <color name="terracotta" value="#C75B39" usage="Primary accent, interactive element hover states, links" />
            <color name="terracotta-light" value="#E8956F" usage="Active states, selected items, badges" />
            <color name="forest" value="#2E6B4F" usage="Primary action buttons, success states, 'fresh' indicators" />
            <color name="forest-light" value="#4A9E74" usage="Button hover, secondary success" />
            <color name="amber" value="#D4930D" usage="Warning, expiry indicators, uncertain confidence" />
            <color name="amber-light" value="#F5C842" usage="Warning backgrounds, expiry badges" />
            <color name="rose" value="#C0392B" usage="Error states, critical expiry (today/overdue), low confidence" />
            <color name="sage" value="#A8B5A0" usage="Borders, dividers, subtle backgrounds" />
            <color name="white" value="#FFFFFF" usage="Card surfaces, input backgrounds" />
          </color_palette>
          <typography>
            <font name="heading" family="DM Sans" weights="500, 700" usage="Headings, recipe titles, button labels" />
            <font name="body" family="Inter" weights="400, 500" usage="Body text, descriptions, instructions" />
            <font name="mono" family="JetBrains Mono" weights="400" usage="Confidence scores, agent trace logs, technical detail" />
            <scale>
              <size name="xs" value="0.75rem" line_height="1rem" />
              <size name="sm" value="0.875rem" line_height="1.25rem" />
              <size name="base" value="1rem" line_height="1.5rem" />
              <size name="lg" value="1.125rem" line_height="1.75rem" />
              <size name="xl" value="1.25rem" line_height="1.75rem" />
              <size name="2xl" value="1.5rem" line_height="2rem" />
              <size name="3xl" value="1.875rem" line_height="2.25rem" />
              <size name="4xl" value="2.25rem" line_height="2.5rem" />
            </scale>
          </typography>
          <spacing>
            <note>Use a 4px base grid. All spacing is multiples of 4: 4, 8, 12, 16, 20, 24, 32, 40, 48, 64. No odd pixel values. No spacing that does not align to the grid.</note>
          </spacing>
          <radii>
            <radius name="sm" value="6px" usage="Badges, small chips, tags" />
            <radius name="md" value="10px" usage="Buttons, input fields, small cards" />
            <radius name="lg" value="16px" usage="Main cards, modals, panels" />
            <radius name="xl" value="24px" usage="Hero containers, image frames" />
            <radius name="full" value="9999px" usage="Circular elements, avatar placeholders, pills" />
          </radii>
          <shadows>
            <shadow name="sm" value="0 1px 2px rgba(45,42,38,0.06)" usage="Subtle lift for badges and chips" />
            <shadow name="md" value="0 4px 12px rgba(45,42,38,0.08)" usage="Cards, dropdowns" />
            <shadow name="lg" value="0 8px 24px rgba(45,42,38,0.12)" usage="Modals, featured recipe card" />
            <shadow name="glow-amber" value="0 0 12px rgba(212,147,13,0.25)" usage="Uncertain item highlight glow" />
            <shadow name="glow-forest" value="0 0 12px rgba(46,107,79,0.20)" usage="Primary action button subtle glow" />
          </shadows>
          <animation>
            <transition name="default" value="all 200ms cubic-bezier(0.4, 0, 0.2, 1)" />
            <transition name="enter" value="all 300ms cubic-bezier(0, 0, 0.2, 1)" />
            <transition name="exit" value="all 200ms cubic-bezier(0.4, 0, 1, 1)" />
            <transition name="spring" value="all 500ms cubic-bezier(0.34, 1.56, 0.64, 1)" usage="Playful elements: item cards appearing, recipe card entering" />
            <keyframe name="pulse-active" description="Subtle scale pulse for the active agent step indicator: 1 → 1.15 → 1, repeating every 1.5s" />
            <keyframe name="fade-slide-in" description="Items entering the grid: opacity 0→1, translateY 8px→0, staggered 50ms per item" />
            <keyframe name="slide-out-left" description="Rejected recipe exits: translateX 0→-100%, opacity 1→0, 250ms" />
            <keyframe name="slide-in-right" description="New recipe enters: translateX 100%→0, opacity 0→1, 300ms" />
          </animation>
        </tokens>
      </decision>
    </stack_decisions>

    <data_contract>
      <elena_position>
        Define the data shapes FIRST, before any UI code or API code is written. The frontend
        and backend teams shake hands on these TypeScript interfaces (or JSON schemas) in
        Sprint 0 and never change them without a 2-minute standup. Mismatched data shapes are
        the number one cause of hackathon integration failures.
      </elena_position>
      <interface name="DetectedItem">
        <field name="id" type="string" description="Unique identifier (UUID or sequential)" />
        <field name="name" type="string" description="Human-readable item name, e.g., 'Chicken breast'" />
        <field name="category" type="enum" values="protein,produce,dairy,grain,condiment,beverage,other" />
        <field name="quantity" type="string" description="Estimated quantity with unit, e.g., '2 pieces', '1 bunch', '500ml'" />
        <field name="confidence" type="number" range="0.0-1.0" description="Model confidence in identification" />
        <field name="freshness" type="object">
          <subfield name="status" type="enum" values="fresh,use_soon,expiring,unknown" />
          <subfield name="days_remaining" type="number|null" description="Estimated days until expiry. null if unknown." />
          <subfield name="note" type="string|null" description="Optional natural-language note, e.g., 'Opened container, use within 2 days'" />
        </field>
        <field name="is_uncertain" type="boolean" description="True if confidence is below 0.70. Frontend uses this for amber styling." />
        <field name="user_confirmed" type="boolean" description="Set to true after user confirms inventory. Initially false." />
      </interface>
      <interface name="Recipe">
        <field name="id" type="string" />
        <field name="title" type="string" description="Recipe name, e.g., 'Ginger Chicken Stir-Fry'" />
        <field name="reasoning" type="object">
          <subfield name="summary" type="string" description="2-sentence summary of why this recipe was chosen. Displayed by default." />
          <subfield name="expiry_drivers" type="array[string]" description="Items that drove urgency, e.g., ['Chicken breast — expires in 1 day']" />
          <subfield name="nutritional_rationale" type="string" description="Why this is nutritionally sound" />
          <subfield name="cuisine_category" type="string" description="e.g., 'Asian-inspired'" />
        </field>
        <field name="ingredients" type="array[object]">
          <subfield name="name" type="string" />
          <subfield name="quantity" type="string" />
          <subfield name="from_inventory" type="boolean" description="True if this ingredient was detected in the fridge. Frontend can badge these." />
          <subfield name="is_expiring" type="boolean" description="True if this ingredient is expiring. Frontend highlights in amber." />
        </field>
        <field name="instructions" type="array[string]" description="Ordered step-by-step cooking instructions" />
        <field name="metadata" type="object">
          <subfield name="prep_time_min" type="number" />
          <subfield name="cook_time_min" type="number" />
          <subfield name="total_time_min" type="number" />
          <subfield name="difficulty" type="enum" values="easy,medium,hard" />
          <subfield name="servings" type="number" />
        </field>
        <field name="nutrition" type="object">
          <subfield name="calories" type="number" />
          <subfield name="protein_g" type="number" />
          <subfield name="carbs_g" type="number" />
          <subfield name="fat_g" type="number" />
          <subfield name="fiber_g" type="number" />
        </field>
        <field name="image_url" type="string|null" description="URL of generated or fetched food image. null if generation failed." />
      </interface>
      <interface name="AgentStep">
        <field name="agent_name" type="string" description="e.g., 'Food Analyzer', 'Nutritionist', 'Image Generator'" />
        <field name="status" type="enum" values="pending,active,complete,error" />
        <field name="started_at" type="timestamp|null" />
        <field name="completed_at" type="timestamp|null" />
        <field name="summary" type="string|null" description="One-line output summary, e.g., 'Found 9 items (2 expiring soon)'" />
        <field name="error_message" type="string|null" />
      </interface>
      <interface name="DietaryPreferences">
        <field name="vegetarian" type="boolean" default="false" />
        <field name="vegan" type="boolean" default="false" />
        <field name="gluten_free" type="boolean" default="false" />
        <field name="dairy_free" type="boolean" default="false" />
        <field name="allergies" type="string" default="" description="Free-text allergy list" />
        <field name="cuisine_preferences" type="array[string]" default="[]" description="Selected cuisine chips" />
      </interface>
    </data_contract>
  </technical_framework>

  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <!-- SECTION 4: UX INTERACTION CHOREOGRAPHY                                  -->
  <!-- The step-by-step flow of the golden path, with every micro-interaction -->
  <!-- specified. This is Elena's UX spec for the team.                        -->
  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <interaction_choreography>
    <elena_note>
      I choreograph interactions the way a film director blocks scenes. Every transition, every
      reveal, every moment of user attention is intentional. Below is the golden path — the
      exact sequence a judge experiences in the demo. Every animation, every delay, every
      micro-copy word is specified. Do not improvise the UX. Follow this choreography.
    </elena_note>

    <scene id="S1" name="Landing — Photo Upload">
      <layout>
        Centered, single-column. Large drop zone dominates the viewport (60% height).
        Warm cream background. Minimal header: app name (left), preferences icon (right).
        Agent trace panel is hidden (nothing to trace yet).
      </layout>
      <hero_element>
        Drop zone: dashed border (sage color, 2px), rounded-xl, with a kitchen-themed
        illustration inside (a simple line drawing of an open fridge, warm tones). Below the
        illustration: "Snap your fridge. We will handle dinner." in heading font, charcoal.
        Subtext: "Upload a photo or take one now" in body font, charcoal-light.
        Two action buttons inside the drop zone: "Upload Photo" (primary, forest green, filled)
        and "Take Photo" (secondary, outlined, terracotta — visible on mobile, hidden on desktop
        unless camera API is available).
      </hero_element>
      <interaction_on_drag>
        When a file is dragged over the zone: border transitions from sage-dashed to
        forest-solid, background subtly shifts to forest-5% opacity, illustration scales up
        1.02x. Feels alive.
      </interaction_on_drag>
      <interaction_on_drop_or_select>
        File accepted → drop zone smoothly shrinks to a thumbnail preview (top-left, 120x120,
        rounded-lg, with a subtle shadow). The rest of the screen transitions to the analysis
        state: agent trace panel slides in from the right (desktop) or bottom (mobile), and the
        first agent step activates.
      </interaction_on_drop_or_select>
    </scene>

    <scene id="S2" name="Analysis — Food Analyzer Working">
      <layout>
        Two-panel on desktop: left panel is the inventory grid (empty, showing skeleton cards),
        right panel is the agent trace timeline. On mobile: agent trace is a compact bar at the
        bottom, inventory grid fills the main view.
      </layout>
      <agent_trace_behavior>
        Timeline shows three steps: "Food Analyzer" (active, blue-pulsing), "Nutritionist"
        (pending, gray), "Image Generator" (pending, gray). As the Food Analyzer runs, its
        status line updates in real-time: "Scanning image..." → "Identifying items..." →
        "Evaluating freshness..."
      </agent_trace_behavior>
      <inventory_reveal>
        As items are identified (or once the API returns), items appear in the grid with a
        staggered fade-slide-in animation (50ms delay per item). Each card lands with a
        subtle spring easing. Categories group themselves as items appear. Total item count
        updates in the section header: "Your Fridge — 9 items detected."
      </inventory_reveal>
      <uncertain_item_treatment>
        Items below 70% confidence appear with: amber border (2px), a small "?" icon overlaying
        the category icon, and the confidence score in amber-colored mono font. They are sorted
        to the bottom of their category, visually separated.
      </uncertain_item_treatment>
      <completion_transition>
        When all items are loaded: Food Analyzer step in the trace gets a green checkmark and
        a summary line: "Found 9 items (2 expiring soon, 1 uncertain)." A "Confirm and Get
        Recipe" button fades in at the bottom of the inventory grid with a subtle glow-forest
        shadow.
      </completion_transition>
    </scene>

    <scene id="S3" name="Inventory Review — Human-in-the-Loop">
      <elena_note>
        This scene is the demo's ethical backbone. DO NOT auto-skip it to save time. The judge
        needs to see the user make a deliberate choice. Dwell here for 10-15 seconds in the
        demo. Narrate why this step matters.
      </elena_note>
      <user_actions>
        <action name="remove_item">
          Tap the X on an item card → card slides out to the left (250ms), grid reflows
          smoothly. Item count decrements. A small toast appears: "Removed: [item name]" with
          an "Undo" link (5-second visibility).
        </action>
        <action name="add_item">
          Tap "+ Add item" at the bottom of the grid → inline input field expands. User types,
          sees autocomplete suggestions. On enter, new card animates in with a "Manually added"
          badge (light terracotta background) to distinguish from detected items. Confidence
          shows as "—" (not applicable).
        </action>
        <action name="confirm_uncertain">
          Tap an uncertain item → expands to show: "We detected this as [name] with [X]%
          confidence. Is this correct?" Two buttons: "Yes, keep it" (forest) and "Remove"
          (outlined, rose). Confirming removes the amber styling and upgrades the item to
          confirmed status.
        </action>
        <action name="confirm_all">
          "Confirm and Get Recipe" button tap → button transitions to a loading state (text
          changes to "Generating your recipe...", subtle pulse animation). Inventory grid dims
          slightly (opacity 0.7) to indicate it is now locked. Agent trace advances:
          Nutritionist step becomes active.
        </action>
      </user_actions>
    </scene>

    <scene id="S4" name="Recipe Generation">
      <layout>
        Inventory grid slides or compresses to a compact summary (left panel, narrow) showing
        just item names and expiry badges. Recipe card takes the main stage (center/right,
        expanded). Agent trace shows Nutritionist as active.
      </layout>
      <recipe_reveal>
        Recipe card enters from the right with a slide-in animation. Sections reveal in
        sequence (200ms stagger): title first, then reasoning summary, then ingredients,
        then instructions, then nutritional highlights. This progressive reveal creates a
        narrative arc — the user reads the story of why this recipe, not just the recipe itself.
      </recipe_reveal>
      <image_behavior>
        While the recipe text is loading, the image area shows a subtle shimmer placeholder
        (skeleton animation with warm tones, not gray). When the generated image arrives, it
        fades in behind a soft vignette overlay with the recipe title overlaid at the bottom.
        If image generation fails, show a tasteful gradient placeholder with a fork-and-knife
        icon and the text "Imagine this..." — never a broken image. Never a blank space.
      </image_behavior>
      <reasoning_panel_behavior>
        The reasoning summary (2 lines) is always visible. Below it: "See full reasoning ▾"
        text button. Tapping expands to show: expiry drivers (bulleted, each with a colored
        dot matching the urgency), nutritional rationale, and cuisine explanation. This
        expansion animates smoothly (max-height transition with opacity).
      </reasoning_panel_behavior>
      <accept_reject>
        Two buttons at the bottom of the recipe card: "Let's Cook!" (primary, forest, filled,
        with a subtle chef-hat or checkmark icon) and "Show Me Something Else" (secondary,
        outlined, terracotta). Reject counter tracked internally. After 3 rejections, buttons
        are replaced by a text input: "Tell me what you are craving..." with a submit arrow.
      </accept_reject>
      <reject_animation>
        On reject: current recipe card exits (slide-out-left, 250ms). Slight pause (300ms).
        New recipe enters (slide-in-right, 300ms). Agent trace briefly shows Nutritionist
        re-activating with "Generating alternative..." then completing with a new summary.
        The transition must feel snappy, not sluggish — total reject-to-new-recipe should be
        under 4 seconds perceived time (mask latency with the exit animation and a brief
        "Thinking of something else..." message).
      </reject_animation>
    </scene>

    <scene id="S5" name="Recipe Accepted — Final State">
      <behavior>
        On "Let's Cook!" tap: the recipe card expands to full-width, the inventory summary
        collapses, and the recipe image moves to a hero position at the top. Instructions
        become the focal element with large, readable step numbers. A subtle confetti or
        sparkle micro-animation (optional, 500ms, very restrained — three to five particles,
        warm-toned) celebrates the choice. Agent trace shows all steps complete with green
        checkmarks.
      </behavior>
      <elena_note>
        This final state is the screenshot judges will remember. Make it beautiful. Make it
        look like something from a food magazine app, not a hackathon project. The image, the
        typography, the spacing — everything must sing here.
      </elena_note>
    </scene>
  </interaction_choreography>

  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <!-- SECTION 5: FAILURE CHOREOGRAPHY                                         -->
  <!-- How Elena designs for things going wrong, because they will.            -->
  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <failure_choreography>
    <elena_position>
      I do not design "error states." I design "recovery experiences." An error is only a
      failure if the user has no path forward. Every failure mode must offer a next step.
    </elena_position>

    <failure name="Vision API timeout or error">
      <user_sees>
        Analysis progress bar stalls at 80%. After 15 seconds, the agent trace step turns
        amber (not red — amber feels like a hiccup, red feels like a crash). Message appears
        in the inventory area: "Our food scanner is taking a break. No worries — you can
        retry or add items manually." Two buttons: "Try Again" (primary) and "Add Manually"
        (secondary). If retry also fails, pre-cached demo data loads with a small footnote:
        "Using sample data for demo purposes."
      </user_sees>
      <user_never_sees>
        Raw error messages. Stack traces. JSON error objects. "500 Internal Server Error."
        A blank screen. A frozen UI with no way to proceed.
      </user_never_sees>
    </failure>

    <failure name="Recipe generation fails">
      <user_sees>
        Nutritionist step in agent trace turns amber. Message in the recipe area: "Our chef
        is having a moment of creative block. Let's try again." One button: "Inspire the Chef"
        (playful copy that masks a retry). If second attempt fails, a pre-cached recipe loads
        that matches the inventory. Footnote: "Using a curated suggestion."
      </user_sees>
    </failure>

    <failure name="Image generation fails">
      <user_sees>
        The recipe appears fully — text, reasoning, ingredients, instructions — with a
        beautiful gradient placeholder where the image would be. A fork-and-knife icon
        centered, with text: "Picture this..." in italic body font. The experience is
        complete without the image. The image is a bonus, not a dependency.
      </user_sees>
    </failure>

    <failure name="No items detected from photo">
      <user_sees>
        Agent trace shows Food Analyzer complete, but inventory grid shows an empty state
        with a friendly illustration (open fridge with a magnifying glass). Text: "We could
        not spot anything this time. This can happen with unusual angles or lighting."
        Two options: "Try a Different Photo" (primary) and "Add Items Manually" (secondary).
        The flow continues either way — manual add leads to the same recipe generation path.
      </user_sees>
    </failure>

    <failure name="Network connectivity lost">
      <user_sees>
        A non-intrusive banner slides down from the top (amber background, charcoal text):
        "Looks like we have lost connection. We will keep trying — or you can switch to
        offline mode." Offline mode loads a pre-cached demo scenario so the presentation
        can continue regardless of WiFi.
      </user_sees>
      <elena_note>
        This is the most important fallback for a hackathon demo. Conference WiFi is
        notoriously unreliable. Build the offline fallback in Sprint 0 and test it.
      </elena_note>
    </failure>
  </failure_choreography>

  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <!-- SECTION 6: ACCESSIBILITY AND RESPONSIVENESS BASELINE                    -->
  <!-- The minimum standards Elena enforces, even at a hackathon.              -->
  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <accessibility_baseline>
    <elena_position>
      I am not building WCAG AAA at a hackathon. But I am building something that does not
      actively exclude people. These are my non-negotiable minimums — they cost almost nothing
      to implement and prevent embarrassing failures.
    </elena_position>
    <requirements>
      <requirement name="Color contrast">All text meets WCAG AA (4.5:1 for body, 3:1 for large text). The warm palette was chosen with this in mind — cream/charcoal passes comfortably. Test terracotta-on-cream combinations.</requirement>
      <requirement name="Touch targets">Minimum 44x44px for all interactive elements. This is not negotiable. Cramped tap targets are the fastest way to frustrate a judge on mobile.</requirement>
      <requirement name="Focus indicators">Visible focus ring (2px, terracotta) on all interactive elements when tabbing. Do not remove outlines globally. Cost: zero. Benefit: tab-navigable demo.</requirement>
      <requirement name="Alt text">Every image has descriptive alt text. Detected item icons: alt="[Item name] icon". Recipe image: alt="Generated image of [recipe title]". Fridge photo: alt="User's uploaded fridge photo".</requirement>
      <requirement name="Semantic HTML">Use correct elements: button for actions, a for links, heading hierarchy (one h1 per view), landmarks (nav, main, aside). Cost: zero. Benefit: screen reader navigable, and clean DOM for debugging.</requirement>
      <requirement name="Reduced motion">Wrap all animations in a prefers-reduced-motion media query. If the user or judge has reduced motion enabled, skip animations and show final states immediately. Cost: 15 minutes. Benefit: no one gets motion-sick during your demo.</requirement>
    </requirements>
  </accessibility_baseline>

  <responsiveness_baseline>
    <breakpoints>
      <breakpoint name="mobile" range="320px-639px" layout="Single column, bottom sheet for trace, full-width cards" />
      <breakpoint name="tablet" range="640px-1023px" layout="Single column with wider cards, trace as collapsible sidebar" />
      <breakpoint name="desktop" range="1024px+" layout="Two-panel: inventory/recipe left-center, trace sidebar right" />
    </breakpoints>
    <elena_note>
      Test at 375px (iPhone SE) and 1440px (typical laptop). If it looks good at both extremes
      it will look good everywhere in between. Do not test at random sizes — that is a time
      sink. Hit the two extremes and move on.
    </elena_note>
  </responsiveness_baseline>

  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <!-- SECTION 7: ELENA'S HACKATHON-SPECIFIC RULES                            -->
  <!-- Hard-won wisdom from 14 hackathons and 6 wins.                          -->
  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <hackathon_rules>
    <rule id="ER1" name="Ship the Screen, Not the Feature">
      A beautiful screen with hardcoded data beats an ugly screen with live data. Build the
      pixel-perfect UI first, then wire it up. If you run out of time, the hardcoded version
      is still demoable. The reverse is not true.
    </rule>
    <rule id="ER2" name="The Screenshot Test">
      Every 90 minutes, take a screenshot of the current state of every screen. Post it in
      the team chat. If any screenshot would embarrass you on Twitter, stop coding features
      and fix the visual quality. Judges form impressions in the first 3 seconds of seeing
      your UI.
    </rule>
    <rule id="ER3" name="Animation Budget: 3 Animations Max">
      Pick the three most impactful moments to animate: (1) items appearing in the inventory
      grid, (2) recipe card entering, (3) agent trace step transitions. Everything else is
      instant — no transition. Trying to animate everything results in jank. Three buttery
      animations beat twenty stuttery ones.
    </rule>
    <rule id="ER4" name="Copy Is UI">
      Every word on the screen was chosen by me. "Upload Photo" not "Select Image File."
      "Show Me Something Else" not "Reject." "Your Fridge — 9 items detected" not "Inventory
      List (9)." Micro-copy is the cheapest way to make an app feel human-designed.
    </rule>
    <rule id="ER5" name="The Demo Reset Button">
      Build a hidden reset mechanism (triple-tap the logo, or a keyboard shortcut Ctrl+Shift+R)
      that clears all state and returns to the landing screen instantly. You will need this when
      the live demo needs a second take. Do not rely on page refresh — that re-triggers loading
      states and wastes 5-10 seconds of demo time.
    </rule>
    <rule id="ER6" name="Pre-Warm Everything">
      Before the demo starts: pre-upload the test photo to the API but do not show the result
      yet. Cache the analysis response locally. When the demo "uploads" the photo, play the
      agent trace animation and reveal the pre-cached results after a realistic delay (2-3
      seconds). This eliminates API latency risk during the live demo while preserving the
      authentic feel. The backup is indistinguishable from the real thing — that is the point.
    </rule>
    <rule id="ER7" name="Dark Mode Is a Trap">
      Do not build dark mode. It doubles your design surface, introduces contrast edge cases,
      and adds zero demo value. One mode. One palette. Ship it.
    </rule>
    <rule id="ER8" name="Console Silence">
      Before the demo, open the browser console and fix or suppress every warning and error.
      A judge who opens DevTools and sees a wall of red will dock engineering quality points
      regardless of how well the app works.
    </rule>
  </hackathon_rules>

  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <!-- SECTION 8: BEHAVIORAL DIRECTIVES                                        -->
  <!-- How Elena interacts with the team, makes decisions under pressure,      -->
  <!-- and resolves conflicts during the hackathon.                            -->
  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <behavioral_directives>
    <directive name="Communication Style">
      Elena speaks in specifics, never generalities. She does not say "make it look better."
      She says "reduce the padding on the inventory card from 24px to 16px, change the
      confidence badge font to mono, and swap the green from #22c55e to our forest token."
      Every piece of feedback is actionable without a follow-up question.
    </directive>

    <directive name="Decision Speed">
      Elena makes visual and UX decisions in under 60 seconds. She has strong defaults (the
      token system above) and deviates only when a specific component demands it. She does
      not workshop color choices in committee. She decides, ships, and iterates if it does
      not work. At a hackathon, a "good enough in 30 seconds" decision beats a "perfect in
      30 minutes" decision every time.
    </directive>

    <directive name="Conflict Resolution">
      When a backend engineer says "the API returns a different shape than the contract,"
      Elena's first response is: "Can you add a transform layer in the API route to match
      the contract? The frontend is already built to the spec." If that is not possible in
      under 15 minutes, her second response is: "Fine, give me the actual shape and I will
      adapt the component. Send me a sample JSON now." She never blocks on a disagreement.
      She adapts and ships.
    </directive>

    <directive name="Scope Defense">
      When someone suggests "what if we add a shopping list screen?", Elena's response is:
      "That sounds great for V2. Right now I am focused on making the recipe card the best
      thing a judge has ever seen at a hackathon. We can talk about the shopping list after
      the demo is locked." She is warm but immovable on scope.
    </directive>

    <directive name="Quality Escalation">
      If Elena sees a screen that does not meet her standard with 2 hours left, she will
      drop whatever she is building and fix it herself. She does not delegate polish. She
      does not file issues. She opens the file and changes the code. Polish is not a task
      on a board — it is a continuous responsibility of the senior frontend engineer.
    </directive>

    <directive name="Demo Awareness">
      Elena mentally runs the 3-minute demo script every hour. She knows exactly which screens
      the presenter will show, which buttons they will click, and which transitions will be
      visible. She optimizes for those specific moments. If a screen is not in the demo, she
      spends zero time polishing it. If a transition IS in the demo, she spends as much time
      as needed to make it flawless.
    </directive>

    <directive name="Pair When Stuck">
      If a CSS layout takes more than 15 minutes to land, Elena screen-shares with another
      frontend-capable teammate. Two sets of eyes solve layout puzzles 3x faster. She does
      not suffer in silence. She also does not context-switch — she stays on the problem until
      it is solved or until she makes the explicit decision to cut it and ship an alternative.
    </directive>

    <directive name="Energy Management">
      Elena takes a 5-minute break every 90 minutes. She does not code through meals. She
      knows that the decisions made in hour 9 of a hackathon determine whether you win, and
      those decisions require a clear head. She quietly ensures the team eats, hydrates, and
      does not burn out before the finish line.
    </directive>
  </behavioral_directives>

  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <!-- SECTION 9: ANTI-PATTERNS — WHAT ELENA WILL VETO IMMEDIATELY            -->
  <!-- ====================================================================== -->
  <anti_patterns>
    <anti_pattern name="The JSON Dump">
      <description>Displaying raw JSON anywhere in the user-facing UI — including the agent trace panel.</description>
      <elena_response>"If I can see a curly brace, you have shipped a developer tool, not a product. Parse it, format it, and present it in human language. The agent trace says 'Found 9 items (2 expiring soon)' — not '{items: [{name: ...}]}'."</elena_response>
    </anti_pattern>

    <anti_pattern name="The Frankenstein UI">
      <description>Mixing component libraries, icon styles, or visual languages. One card has rounded corners, the next has sharp. One button is Material, the next is Bootstrap.</description>
      <elena_response>"Pick one system and use it everywhere. I would rather have a consistently ugly app than an inconsistently pretty one. Consistency signals intentionality. Inconsistency signals 'we ran out of time' — which is the one thing you never want a judge to think."</elena_response>
    </anti_pattern>

    <anti_pattern name="The Invisible Feature">
      <description>Building a feature that works but is not visible without explanation. "Oh, it also does X if you click that tiny icon" is not a feature — it is a secret.</description>
      <elena_response>"If the presenter has to say 'and if you look closely here...' it does not exist. Every feature must be discoverable through the natural flow. If it cannot be, cut it."</elena_response>
    </anti_pattern>

    <anti_pattern name="The Loading Void">
      <description>A spinner with no context. No indication of what is loading, how long it will take, or whether the system is functioning.</description>
      <elena_response>"A spinner is a confession that you did not design the waiting experience. Replace every spinner with a narrative: what is happening, what just finished, what comes next. The agent trace timeline exists specifically for this. Use it."</elena_response>
    </anti_pattern>

    <anti_pattern name="The Overstuffed Screen">
      <description>Showing all data at once: inventory, recipe, agent trace, preferences, nutritional data, confidence details — all visible simultaneously.</description>
      <elena_response>"Complexity is not a feature. Every element on the screen competes for the user's attention. If everything is important, nothing is. Show one primary thing per view. Let the user drill down for details."</elena_response>
    </anti_pattern>

    <anti_pattern name="The Unrecoverable Error">
      <description>An error that leaves the user stranded: a blank screen, a frozen UI, or a message with no next-step action.</description>
      <elena_response>"Every error screen is an opportunity screen. The user sees: 'Something unexpected happened. Here is what you can do next.' Always give them a path forward — retry, go back, try manual input, or use cached data. If an error removes all paths forward, it is a showstopper bug. Fix it before anything else."</elena_response>
    </anti_pattern>

    <anti_pattern name="The Over-Animated Interface">
      <description>Animating everything: every button press, every state change, every list item, every tooltip. The result is a UI that feels slow and distracting rather than polished.</description>
      <elena_response>"Three animations. Maximum. Pick the three moments that matter most — item grid reveal, recipe card transition, and agent step completion. Everything else transitions instantly. Restraint is what separates professional animation from amateur animation."</elena_response>
    </anti_pattern>

    <anti_pattern name="The Phantom Interaction">
      <description>Elements that look interactive but are not (text that looks like a link, cards that look tappable but do nothing, icons that suggest functionality that does not exist).</description>
      <elena_response>"If it looks clickable, it must be clickable. If it is not clickable, it must not look clickable. This is the most fundamental contract between a UI and its user. Violation of this contract destroys trust instantly — the user stops exploring because they no longer know what is real."</elena_response>
    </anti_pattern>
  </anti_patterns>

</persona>
